Guide to the Reston Association records, 1964-2006
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 6: Committee, 1969-2000; (2 boxes)
  - Blue Ribbon Committee on Raising the Assessment Cap-Status Quo Sub-Committee Report, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    17.11
  - Board of Directors-Fiscal Committee, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    426.30
  - Committees, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    16.25
  - Committee Information, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    537.6
  - Community Relations Committee, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    529.20
  - Dog Committee, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    529.26
  - Education Committee, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    529.21
  - Elderly Center, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    528.6
  - Elections Committee, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    529.27
  - General Material: bylaws About Reston Community Association, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    529.14
  - Governance Committee, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    529.23
  - Health Committee, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    528.5
  - Health Care Changes at Reston Community Association, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    528.7
  - Housing Committee, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    529.24
  - Miscellaneous Materials, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    529.12
  - Plan Amendment and Task Force, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    537.11
  - Planning Commission, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    537.14
  - Planning and Zoning Miscellaneous, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    527.24
  - Planning and Zoning, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    527.25
  - Planning and Zoning, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    527.26
  - Planning and Zoning Committee, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    529.22
  - Report of Citizens Committee, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Reston Community Association Governance Committee, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Reston Motion Task Force, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    511.5
  - Safety Committee, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    529.25
  - Transportation Committee, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    529.19
  - Zoning, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    537.17
- Series 7: Articles, 1964-2005; (2 boxes)
  Series 7 consists of articles relating to Reston. The articles cover a variety of topics such as elections, grand openings, community newsletters, and other community functions. The articles are from papers from The Connection, a local Fairfax newspaper, The Washington Post and other publications.
  - "A Natural Progression to the Lake Anne community Center in 1998" by Jane Gilmer Wilhelm-Presented to the RCC Board of Directors (Box 27, Folder 10)
    531.2
  - Article on Chloethiel Woodard Smith, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 11)
    531.28
  - Articles on Reston Real Estate, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 12)
    531.31
  - Articles on Geological Survey Laboratory, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    531.29
  - Deed of Gift-From There to Here, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    535.7
  - Election, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    527.33
  - Expo, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    536.19
  - Governance (Newsclippings), 1990s (Box 27, Folder 17)
    527.2
  - Grand Opening of Hunters Woods, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 18)
    537.31
  - Herndon and Reston Historical Overview, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    536.1
  - Industrial Reston, Community Services, Population, Street Map and Rental Map, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    536.18
  - Journal of the American Planning Association (Volume 46, Number 4), 1980 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    1.02
  - Magazines, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 1)
    534.7
  - Metro to Dulles/Airport Authority, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    16.05
  - Miscellaneous Information by RCC for Reston Residents, 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    531.11
  - News Articles, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 4)
    537.16
  - Newspaper Articles on Reston Dedication, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    531.27
  - Newspaper Articles on Reston Takeover by Gulf Oil Corporation, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    531.30
  - Newsletter (Volume 1, Number 1), 1960s (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, 1980s (Box 28, Folder 8)
    528.8
  - "No Cease Fire on Horizon for Reston Association Board"-The Connection, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    17.07
  - Press Releases, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    529.18
  - Prime Times, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    535.1
  - Publications Featuring Reston, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    506.5
  - Responses to Haas' Call for a "Nature House" by Joe Leighton, 2000s (Box 28, Folder 13)
    17.08
  - Reston Article-Monsanto Magazine, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    531.4
  - Reston Article-Cover of Business Week, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    531.6
  - Reston Article-Urban Land "What Buyers Think of Reston", 1966 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    531.7
  - Reston Article-Washington Post "Reston Counts 1000 Residents and Looks Like New Town", 1966 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Reston Article-The Commonwealth "Reston: A New Town for a New Kind of Life", 1966 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    531.9
  - Reston Article-Industrial Design "Brave New Town", 1964 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    531.10
  - Reston Article-House and Homes "New Townhouse Design for the Higher-Income Market", 1965 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Reston Article-The New Republic "The Community: Could This be Our Town?", 1964 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    531.12
  - Reston Article-American County Government "Modern Zoning for Reston", 1967 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    531.13
  - Reston Article-Columbia Real Estate Newsletter "Famed New City of Reston, Virginia, Shows Extensive Growth", 1967 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    531.14
  - Reston Article-Washington World "Reston, Virginia, Is Work Play Eden Near Capital", 1964 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    531.15
  - Reston Article-Industrial Property Guide "Reston: Newest and Finest Research-Industrial Park", 1964 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    531.16
  - Reston Article-The Washingtonian "Reston", 1966 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    531.17
  - Reston Article-Urban Land "What Buyers Think of Reston", 1960s (Box 28, Folder 27)
    531.18
  - Reston Article-Sunday Magazine, The Washington Star "City Builder", 1966 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    531.19
  - Reston Article-Realtor's Headlines Quarterly magazine Section "New Concepts in Real Estate", 1967 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    531.20
  - Reston Article-The New republic "Are We Being En-Gulfed?", 1967 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    531.21
  - Reston Article-Potomac Home Furnishings "Designer's Home", 1966 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    531.22
  - Reston Article-Look Magazine "A Billion-Dollar Bet on a New Way to Live", 1965 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    531.23
  - Reston Article-House and Garden "The Lure of Living in Clustered Houses", 1967 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    531.26
  - Reston Article-The Sun Magazine "Reston: A Dream Gives Way to Economics", 1968 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    531.25
  - Reston Article-The Orange disc "Reston: A City in a Park", 1968 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Reston Article-Newsweek, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    531.5
  - Reston Articles, 1980s (Box 28, Folder 37)
    536.3
  - Reston, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    16.06
  - "Reston Association Candidates Address Complaints"-Reston Times, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    17.06
  - Reston Association Governing Documents, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    16.07
  - Reston Bus, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    530.17
  - Reston Community Association, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    527.31
  - Reston Community Center, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    16.04
  - Reston Land Corporation, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    535.2
  - Reston Neighborhoods Magazine, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    536.10
  - Reston Pathfinder, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    536.9
  - Reston Times, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    536.23
  - Reston Town Center Plan Unveiled and The Best in Northern Virginia, 1990s (Box 29, Folder 2)
    536.20
  - Reston Twentieth Birthday, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    536.6
  - Restonian, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    536.16
  - The Reston Letter, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    536.4
  - The Reston Times, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    536.2
  - The Washington Post-Outlook, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    539.29
  - "Twin Cities" by Carrie Brown, 1990s (Box 29, Folder 8)
    17.05
- Series 8: Handbooks, 1965-2005; (4 boxes)
  There are 27 folders in this series. The folders contain information regarding recommendations, RHOA handbooks and other manuals about the operations and procedures of the Reston Association different projects and programs.
  - A Brief Guide to Reston's Homeowner and Cluster Associations, 1980s (Box 29, Folder 9)
    463.16
  - A Brief Guide to Reston's Homeowner and Cluster Associations, 1980s (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - A Brief Guide to Reston's Homeowner and Cluster Associations, 1980s (Box 29, Folder 11)
    444.7
    - A Brief Guide to Reston's Homeowner and Cluster Associations, ca. 1996 or 1980s?; 1.
  - A Case Study in New Community Management by Karl J. Ingebristen, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    12.16
  - A Survey of Town House Buyers and Prospects, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    533.13
  - Annual Report Reston Homeowners Handbook, 1984 and 1985 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    480.7
  - Appendix C-Weighted Factor Values and Grade Structure, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    509.18
  - Bentana View, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    525.7
  - Brochures, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    524.3
  - Brochures, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    506.2
  - Brochure for Reston Industrial Center, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 19)
    531.3
  - Citizens Handbook, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    537.13
  - Cluster Handbook, 1980s (Box 29, Folder 21)
    506.7
  - Connection, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    509.22
  - Declarations of Covenants, Conditions and Restrictions for Reston Residential Center, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    440.9
  - Dedication, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    535.6
  - Design Guidelines and Design Review Process (2nd Edition), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    439.4
  - Documents Review Committee Recommendations, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    528.4
  - Financial Statements Years Ending, 1986 and 1987 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    429.11
  - Governing Documents of the Reston Association, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    439.1
  - Manual of Operations and Procedures-Reston Homowners Association Common Land, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 8)
    439.12
  - Manual of Operations and Procedures-Reston Homeowners Association Trees, Plants, Vines and Shrubs, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 9)
    439.13
  - Manual of Operations and Procedures-Miscellaneous Items, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 10)
    439.17
  - Manual of Operations and Procedures-Recreation Facilities, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 11)
    439.16
  - Manual of Operations and Procedures-Pathways, Bridges and Signs, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 12)
    439.15
  - Manual of Operations and PRocedures-Reston Homeowners Lake and Ponds, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 13)
    439.14
  - Manual of Operations and Procedures, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 14)
    439.19
  - Manual of Operations and Procedures-Emergency Procedures, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 15)
    439.18
  - Manual of Operations and Procedures-Appendices, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 16)
    439.20
  - Miscellaneous Reston Brochures, 1960s (Box 30, Folder 17)
    525.5
  - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    525.6
  - North Hills Tennis Courts, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    438.1
  - Reston 2000 and Beyond, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    511.3
  - Reston 2000 and Beyond, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    511.2
  - Reston 2000 and Beyond, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    511.4
  - Reston 2000 and Beyond, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    511.7
  - Reston 2000 and Beyond, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    511.6
  - Programs and Service, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Purchasing Procedures, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    439.3
  - Recreation Membership Study, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Residential Community Association: Private Governments in the Intergovernmental System, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    526.15
  - Reston Association Brochures, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    501.3
  - Reston Athletic Club, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    434.6
  - Reston Athletic Club, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    434.7
  - Reston Athletic Club, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    434.8
  - Reston Center for Industry and Government Design Guidelines and Review Process, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    439.2
  - Reston Community Association, 1970s (Box 32, Folder 6)
    530.16
  - Reston Community Association, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    501.1
  - Reston Community Clubs and Special Interest Groups, 2000s (Box 32, Folder 8)
    501.2
  - Reston Directory, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    536.17
  - Reston Handbook, 1994-1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    536.5
  - Reston Homeowners Association (Case Study), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    500.5
  - Reston Publications-Programs Guide, Branching Out, The Exchange, 1998-2000 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    506.1
  - Reston Recreation Master Plan, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    440.1
  - Televote, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    527.5
  - Tenth Annual Homeowners Association (HOA)/Personal Property Owners Association (POA) Workshop, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    427.41
  - The Comprehensive Plan for Fairfax County, Virginia, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    437.11
  - The Residents' Handbook, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    536.7
  - Urban Land, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 9)
    535.5
- Series 9: General Information, 1966-2006; (7 boxes)
  Includes 36 folders with papers from different binders. The information contained within is from various sources dealing with the Reston Association. The folders have information from different projects and programs that the Association was involved in, such as maintenance, volunteer programs in the community, annual reports and information about the board.
  - Addresses, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 10)
    437.15
  - Affordable Housing Issues, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 11)
    537.10
  - Analysis of Costs to Support an Art Center at Lake Anne Plaza, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    16.10
  - Apartment Owner, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    437.10
  - Arts Center Calculations, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    16.14
  - Board Committees, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    428.12
  - Board of Directors Retreat, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    428.21
  - Board of Directors' Calendar, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    427.29
  - Board of Directors Highlights, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    427.40
  - Board of Directors-Miscellaneous Issues, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    434.5
  - Bus Schedules, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    16.08
  - Chronology, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    16.17
  - Cluster Maintenance, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    1.13
  - Community Service Award and Restonian of the Year Award, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    526.1a
  - Community Service Award and Restonian of the Year Award, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    526.1b
  - Constitution Sample, 1990s (Box 34, Folder 6)
    442.6
  - Deed of Dedication of the Reston First Homeowners Association, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    1.8
  - Design Review Board, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    16.26
  - Dictionary Pages, 1990s (Box 34, Folder 9)
    439.5
  - Dulles Corridor, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    526.22
  - Education, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    526.21
  - Elections, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    526.20
  - Employment, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    441.9
  - Employment, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    441.10
  - Employment, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    441.11
  - Facilities Task Force, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    424.5
  - Farmers' Market, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    526.19
  - Festival, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    526.17
  - Festival, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    537.21
  - Festival, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    527.1
  - Festival, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    529.4
  - Festival, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    529.5
  - Festival, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    529.6
  - Festival, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    529.7
  - Festival, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    529.1
  - Festival, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    529.3
  - Festival, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    529.2
  - Founding folder, 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - General Information, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    509.17
  - Golf Course, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    526.16
  - Guests Book, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    535.15
  - Health Issues, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    526.13
  - Housing, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    434.10
  - Housing, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    434.11
  - Housing, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    434.12
  - Housing, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    434.13
  - Housing, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    434.14
  - Housing, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    437.13
  - Housing, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    526.12
  - Lake Anne, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    536.13
  - Library Issues, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    526.7
  - Map of D.C., 1980s (Box 36, Folder 11)
    536.22
  - Map of the County of Fairfax, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    16.11
  - Meadows Farms, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    436.10
  - Memberships, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    535.3
  - Membership, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    528.12
  - Membership, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    528.11
  - Membership and Assessments, 1990s (Box 36, Folder 17)
    440.11
  - Motion by Bob Poppe to Agenda Item "South Lakes High School Proposal", 2002 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    17.18
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    535.16
  - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 37, Folder 3)
    525.4
  - Miscellaneous Event Flyers and Program Guide-Spring, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    16.09
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1990s (Box 37, Folder 5)
    535.9
  - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    509.23
  - Miscellaneous, 1980s-1990s (Box 37, Folder 7)
    437.12
  - Miscellaneous, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    538.1
  - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    538.2
  - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    537.22
  - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    537.23
  - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    537.25
  - Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    537.24
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    530.1
  - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    523.1
  - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    511.8
  - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    511.9
  - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    511.1
  - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    530.7
  - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    530.4
  - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    530.9
  - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    649.03
  - Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    649.04
  - Naturescaping-Appreciating, Preserving and Restoring Reston's Natural Resources, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    16.02
  - Newcomers Nights, 1980s (Box 40, Folder 2)
    527.30
  - North Point, 1980s (Box 40, Folder 3)
    436.3
  - Papers Pertaining to Reston Community Association, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Paper Prepared for the Reston Symposium, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    536.21
  - Plaza America, 1980s (Box 40, Folder 6)
    527.23
  - Pool Usage Information, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    438.3
  - Programs and Database Content, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    537.9
  - PRC Ordinance, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    537.19
  - Related Matter, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    528.1
  - Resolutions, 1990s (Box 40, Folder 11)
    440.12
  - Reston Association, 1989-1990 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    477.14
  - Reston Association: Working Copy of Long-Range Plan, 1989-1993 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    480.49
  - Reston Athletic Club, 1970s-1990s (Box 40, Folder 14)
    440.6
    - Chronology: Background for Pools and Tennis Roll-ins, 1970s-1990s; 1.
  - Reston Community Association, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    480.28
  - Reston Community Association-Spring Festival Home Tour (Map Drawing), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    480.26
  - Reston Community Center, 1970s (Box 40, Folder 17)
    532.1
  - Reston Description, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    537.28
  - Reston Directors, 1970-1990 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Reston Documents and Amendments Thereto, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    439.7
  - Reston Foundation, 1981-1984 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    528.10
  - Reston Regional Library Dedication, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    537.26
  - Reston Virginia Foundation for Community Associations, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    1.18
  - Restonian of the Year Award, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    529.8
  - Robert E. Simon, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    535.8
  - Role, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    527.18
  - South Lakes High School Tennis Enclosure, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    1.2
  - South Lakes High School Tennis Project, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    17.15
  - Statement by Director at Large Bob Poppe-Covered Tennis In the Reston Association, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    17.19
  - Stewart R. Macdonald and Associates, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Stonegate Village Apartments, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    435.7
  - Stonegate Village Apartments, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    435.4
  - Stonegate Village Apartments, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    435.5
  - Stonegate Village Apartments, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    435.6
  - Streetlight Issues, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    537.20
  - Swimming Pool Statistics, 1970s (Box 41, Folder 14)
    1.12
  - Tennis Enclosure-Note: Not Built, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    1.1
  - Tennis Partnership-Bringing the Fun Indoors, 2000s (Box 41, Folder 16)
    17.17
  - Town Center Office Building, 1990s (Box 41, Folder 17)
    537.27
  - Virginia Reston Election Districts, 2000s (Box 41, Folder 18)
    17.09
  - Visitors Center, 1990s (Box 41, Folder 19)
    535.17
  - Volksmarch, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    536.12
- Series 10: Photographs, 1969-2004; (13 boxes)
  Includes 492 folders with papers from different binders. The items within document various programs from the Reston Association from 1969 to 2004. The series includes photographs, slides, contact sheets and negatives. Also include is a section of oversize photographs, contact sheets and negatives at the end of the series.
  - Amenities Binder-Front Material, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    6 contact sheets
  - Amenities Binder-Front Material, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    1 page
  - Amenities Binder-Front Material Photographs, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    2 photographs
  - Amenities Binder-Boat Rentals, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    1 contact sheet
  - Amenities Binder-Boat Rental Photographs, 1980s (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Amenities Binder-Bridge Photographs, 1980s (Box 41, Folder 26)
    8 photographs
  - Amenities Binder-Lake, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    3 contact sheets
  - Amenities Binder-Lakes, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    15 photographs
  - Amenities Binder-Building Photographs, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    9 photographs
  - Amenities Binder-Lakes, 1980s (Box 41, Folder 30)
    13 photographs
  - Amenities Binder-Pathways, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Amenities Binder-Pathways, 1980s (Box 41, Folder 32)
    6 photographs
  - Amenities Binder-Picnic Area, 1980s (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Amenities Binder-Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Amenities Binder-Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Amenities Binder-Nature, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Amenities Binder-Nature, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Camp Binder-Nature Tots, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 3)
    5 contact sheets
  - Camp Binder-Nature Tots, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 4)
    7 photographs
  - Camp Binder-Hug-A-Tree, 1980s-1990s (Box 42, Folder 5)
    8 contact sheets
  - Camp Binder-Hug-A-Tree, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 6)
    4 photographs
  - Camp Binder-Day Camp, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 7)
    15 contact sheets
  - Camp Binder-Day Camp, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 8)
    7 contact sheets
  - Camp Binder-Day Camp, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 9)
    8 negatives
  - Camp Binder-Day Camp, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 10)
    14 photographs
  - Camp Binder-Day Camp, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 11)
    2 pages
  - Camp Binder-Earth Explores Quest, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Camp Binder-Earth Explores Quest, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Community Building-Scenic, Nature, Pathways, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Community Building-Scenic, Nature, Pathways, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 15)
    12 photographs
  - Community Building-Scenic, Nature, Pathways, Maintenance Violation, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Community Building-Scenic, Nature, Pathways, 1989 and 1993 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Community Building, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - DC Pool RAC-Unlabeled Front Material, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    81 slides